{
    "id": "7da1286073024b1aba3ea9d94250bdac",
    "title": "General Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The moderator maintained an ……………………………… manner throughout the furious debate.",
            "description": "Impassive can mean calm or cool.",
            "answers": [
                "impassive",
                "impassioned",
                "impassionate"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "733e5564d6c94f06a08c23ffc7363f29"
        },
        {
            "question": "The class was ………………………….. for the vacation to begin.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "impatient",
                "unpatient",
                "inpatient"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "66eccd2d21ad4e92a2baf87d75c249aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "Try to remain ……………………………….. until you have heard both sides of the story.",
            "description": "Impartial is the correct word.",
            "answers": [
                "unpartial",
                "impartial",
                "dispartial"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "86db4fd7a369423fa9fab6af2b1dd3dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The leader roused the protestors with an ………………………………….. speech.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "impassive",
                "impassioned",
                "passioned"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fd73506c02794ea4b148769b6d30b14e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her parents …………………………… of her going to dances alone.",
            "description": "Disapprove is the correct word. Disapprove means object to.",
            "answers": [
                "disapprove",
                "unapprove",
                "inapprove"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2f9fe33753ef47b5a4795592c25f58df"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ………………………….. from the stitches was not too great.",
            "description": "Discomfort means ache or pain.",
            "answers": [
                "uncomfort",
                "discomfort",
                "incomfort"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "78c19c28aa4d4290ad266cd669a82cb2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The plot was too ………………………………. to make sense.",
            "description": "Disconnected means confused or illogical.",
            "answers": [
                "unconnected",
                "ill-connected",
                "disconnected"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fbd9f309196e418d9bf522aa6a900430"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her character is …………………………….",
            "description": "Impeccable means flawless. ",
            "answers": [
                "unpeccable",
                "impeccable",
                "inpeccable"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b844cb19135f4dfd86b8a7ac2d16f986"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ………………………………. with her dull life.",
            "description": "Discontented means unhappy. ",
            "answers": [
                "uncontented",
                "discontented",
                "miscontented"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ad0f861cc4564e4e85fdd8ceb8301bce"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dense hedge of thorns formed an …………………………………. barrier around the castle.",
            "description": "Impenetrable means impassable.",
            "answers": [
                "inpenetrable",
                "dispenetrable",
                "impenetrable"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c5b158993aab4707a48239ff8dc33a06"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………………. his good name with ugly gossip.",
            "description": "To discredit is to defame.",
            "answers": [
                "uncredited",
                "discredited",
                "miscredited"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1417d41b4d0d4d188173c7b3c76db103"
        },
        {
            "question": "The difference between the two colors is ………………………………",
            "description": "Imperceptible means unnoticeable. ",
            "answers": [
                "imperceptible",
                "unperceptible",
                "disperceptible"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a450c77c91874ac5bf31aad60b5e3d2d"
        }
    ]
}